[
  {
    "question": "What is 0 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "0"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 0 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 0 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 0 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["6", "5", "3", "4"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 0 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["5", "4", "6", "2"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 0 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["4", "5", "2", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["6", "5", "4", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 1 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "7"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 0 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["1", "4", "3", "2"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["3", "2", "4", "1"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["9", "8", "7", "6"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 2 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["7", "6", "9", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 0 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["3", "7", "4", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "4"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 3 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 0 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["2", "3", "5", "4"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["5", "6", "4", "3"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "8"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "8"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "8"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 4 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["9", "4", "6", "7"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 0 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "7"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 1 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "7"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 2 ?",
    "correctId": 3,
    "answers": ["4", "5", "6", "7"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 3 ?",
    "correctId": 0,
    "answers": ["8", "9", "7", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 4 ?",
    "correctId": 1,
    "answers": ["8", "9", "6", "5"]
  },{
    "question": "What is 5 + 5 ?",
    "correctId": 2,
    "answers": ["6", "7", "10", "9"]
  }
]